<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><words><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cable car</H><audio>cable_car.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><NR>1.</NR><D>a vehicle that runs on tracks and is pulled by a moving cable:</D> <X>We took a ride on a cable car in San Francisco.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>a vehicle that hangs from and is pulled by a moving cable, and that carries passengers up and down a mountain:</D> <X>You can go up the Sugar Loaf in Rio on a cable car.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cafe</H><audio>cafe.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a small restaurant that serves drinks and light meals</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>call</H><su>1</su><audio>call.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a loud sound that is made to attract attention; a shout:</D> <X>a call for help</X><dot><X>That bird's call is easy to recognize.</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>an act of telephoning or a conversation on the telephone; a phone call:</D> <X>I'll give you a call this weekend.</X><dot><br><X>a local/long-distance call</X><H>call</H><su>2</su><audio>call.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><CF>call (out) to somebody; call (something) (out)</CF> <D>to say something loudly or to shout in order to attract attention:</D> <X>"Hello, is anybody there?" she called.</X><dot><X>I could hear a voice calling for help.</X><dot><X>Call the kids. Breakfast is ready.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to telephone (somebody/something):</D> <X>Who's calling, please?</X><dot><X>Thank you for calling.</X><dot><X>I'll call you tomorrow.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>to have as a name:</D> <X>This type of apple is called Golden Delicious.</X><dot><X>What was that town called?</X><NR>4.</NR><D>to name or describe a person or thing in a certain way:</D><br><X>My name is Elizabeth, but my friends call me Liz.</X><dot><X>Can you really call this picture "art"?</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>camping</H><audio>camping.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>sleeping or spending a vacation in a tent:</D> <X>Camping is cheaper than staying in hotels.</X><dot><X>a camping trip</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>can</H><audio>can1.mp3</audio>; <i>strong form</i><audio>can2.mp3</audio><PS>modal verb</PS>(<i>negative </i><DR>cannot</DR><audio>cannot.mp3</audio>; <i>negative short form </i><DR>can't</DR><audio>cant.mp3</audio>; <i>past </i><DR>could</DR><audio>could.mp3</audio>; <i>past negative </i><DR>could not</DR>; <i>past negative short form </i><DR>couldn't</DR><audio>couldnt.mp3</audio>) <NR>1.</NR><D>(used for showing that it is possible for somebody/something to do something or that somebody/something has the ability to do something):</D> <X>I can catch a bus from here.</X><dot><X>Can you ride a bike?</X><dot><X>He can't speak French.</X><dot><X>She couldn't answer the question.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>(asking or giving permission):</D> <X>Can I have a drink, please?</X><NR>3.</NR><D>(asking somebody to do something):</D> <X>Can you help me carry these books?</X><NR>4.</NR><D>(offering to do something):</D> <X>Can I help you find anything?</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>car</H><audio>car.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><NR>1.</NR><D>a vehicle with an engine and four wheels that up to five or six people can ride in; automobile; auto:</D><br><X>a new/used car</X><dot><X>Where can I park the car?</X><dot><X>They had a car accident.</X><dot><X>She gave me a ride in her car.</X><dot><X>to get into/out of a car</X><dot><X>a sports car</X><NR>2.</NR><D>one of the separate parts of a train:</D> <X>a dining car</X><dot><br><X>a subway car</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>care</H><audio>care.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><CF> care (about something)</CF> <D>to be worried about or interested in something; to mind:</D> <X>I'm going to be late and my mother will be furious, but I don't care.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>catch</H><audio>catch.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS>(<i>past, past participle </i><DR>caught</DR><audio>caught.mp3</audio>) <NR>1.</NR><D>to take hold of something that is moving, usually with your hand or hands:</D> <X>She threw the ball and he caught it in one hand.</X><dot><X>The dog caught the ball in its mouth.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to get on a form of public transportation:</D> <X>to catch a train/plane</X><NR>3.</NR><D>to get an illness:</D> <X>I have a bad cold. I must have caught it from somebody at work.</X><CF> catch up on something</CF><NR>1.</NR><D>to spend time doing something that you have not been able to do until now:</D> <X>I'll have to go into the office this weekend to catch up on my work.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to find out about things that have happened:</D> <X>Let's have lunch together and catch up on each other's news.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cathedral</H><audio>cathedral.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a large church that is the most important one in a district.</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cauliflower</H><audio>cauliflower.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable, uncountable</bracket><D>a large vegetable with green leaves and a round white center that you eat when it is cooked.</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cellular phone</H><audio>cellular_phone.mp3</audio> (<i>informal </i><DR>cell phone</DR><audio>cell_phone.mp3</audio>)<PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><br><D>a telephone that you can carry around with you and that works by using radio signals.</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>change</H><audio>change.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><CF>change something (for/into something)</CF> <D>to give somebody money and receive the same amount back in money of a different type:</D> <X>Can you change a twenty-dollar bill?</X><dot><X>I'd like to change a hundred dollars into Swiss francs.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to become different or to make somebody/something different:</D> <X>This town has changed a lot since I was young.</X><dot><X>Our plans have changed. We leave in the morning.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>to take, have, or use something instead of something else:</D> <X>to change jobs</X><dot><X>to change a light bulb</X><dot><X>to change direction</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>chaperone</H><su>1</su><audio>chaperone.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>an older person who goes to social events for young people to watch them and to make sure that they behave correctly.</D> <H>chaperone</H><su>2</su><audio>chaperone.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><D>to act as a chaperone for somebody</D> <DR>unchaperoned</DR><PS>adjective</PS><D>without a chaperone</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cheap</H><audio>cheap.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>low in price; costing little money:</D> <X>Oranges are cheap at this time of year.</X><dot><X>It's cheaper to buy a round-trip ticket than two one-way tickets.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>charging low prices:</D> <X>There's a cheap restaurant right around the corner.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>check</H><audio>check.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>to examine or look at something in order to make sure that it is safe, correct, in good condition, whether it has changed, etc.:</D> <X>Check your work carefully for mistakes before you hand it in.</X><dot><X>Don't forget to check your e-mail</X> (= to see if you have any new messages) <NR>2.</NR><D>to write a mark that looks like a V on a form, etc. to show your choice, to show that something is done, etc.:</D> <X>Check the box next to the right answer.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cheese</H><audio>cheese.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>a type of solid food that is made from milk. Cheese is usually white or yellow in color:</D> <X>a cheese sandwich</X><dot><X>Sprinkle the top of the pizza with grated cheese.</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a type of cheese:</D> <X>a wide selection of cheeses</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>chef</H><audio>chef.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a person who works as the chief cook in a hotel, restaurant, etc.</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>chicken</H><audio>chicken.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a bird that people keep for its eggs and its meat.</D><NR>2.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>the meat of this bird:</D> <X>roast chicken</X><dot><X>a chicken sandwich</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>chocolate</H><audio>chocolate.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>a sweet brown substance that you usually buy in the form of a hard block (<i>a bar</i>). Chocolate is made from cocoa beans:</D> <X>milk/dark chocolate</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a small candy that is made from chocolate, usually with a nut or another sweet substance inside:</D> <X>a box of assorted chocolates</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>city</H><audio>city.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS>(<i>plural </i><DR>cities</DR>) <bracket>countable</bracket><D>a large and important town:</D> <X>Venice is one of the most beautiful cities in the world.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>class</H><audio>class.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a group of students who are taught together:</D> <X>Jane and I are in the same class at school.</X><dot><X>The whole class is going to the theater tonight.</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>countable, uncountable</bracket><D>a lesson:</D> <bracket>countable</bracket><X>Classes begin at 9 o'clock in the morning.</X><dot><bracket>uncountable</bracket><X>We watched an interesting video in class.</X> (= during the lesson) <NR>3.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a course in a particular subject:</D> <X>I'm taking four classes this semester.</X><dot><X>My cooking class starts next Wednesday evening.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>clerk</H><audio>clerk.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><NR>1.</NR><D>a person who sells things to people in a store.</D> <NR>2.</NR><D>a person whose job is to do written work or keep records or accounts in an office, a bank, a court of law, etc.</D> <NR>3.</NR>(<i>also </i><DR>desk clerk</DR>) <D>a person whose job is dealing with people arriving at or leaving a hotel:</D> <X>Leave your keys with the desk clerk.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>click</H><audio>click.mp3</audio> (<i>computing</i>) <CF>click (on something)</CF> <D>to choose a particular function or item on a computer screen, etc. by pressing one of the buttons on a mouse:</D> <X>Click on the icon to select a document.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>climb</H><audio>climb.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>to go up mountains, etc. as a sport.</D><NR>2.</NR><D>to move up to the top of something:</D> <X>The cat climbed to the top of the tree.</X><dot><X>to climb a tree/mountain/rope</X><dot><X>She climbed the stairs to the attic.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>clock</H><audio>clock.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>an instrument that shows you what time it is, often found on the wall of a house or building (not worn like a watch):</D> <X>an alarm clock</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>closet</H><audio>closet.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>an area for storing things, with a door, that is built behind the wall of a room:</D> <X>a walk-in closet</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>clothes</H><audio>clothes.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>plural</bracket><D>the things that you wear, e.g. pants, shirts, dresses, coats, etc. (when thought of all together):</D> <X>Take off those wet clothes.</X><dot><X>She was wearing new clothes.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>coffee</H><audio>coffee.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>the roasted seeds (<i>beans</i>) of a tropical bush, made into powder and used for making a drink:</D> <X>Coffee is the country's biggest export.</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>a drink made by adding hot water to coffee beans that have been made into powder:</D> <X>Would you like tea or coffee?</X><dot><X>a cup of coffee</X><NR>3.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a cup of this drink:</D> <X>I'll have a donut and a large coffee with cream and sugar.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>coffee shop</H><audio>coffee_shop.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a small informal restaurant where people go to have fast, cheap meals, coffee, and other drinks (but no alcohol)</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>college</H><audio>college.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><NR>1.</NR>(<i>in the United States</i>) <bracket>countable, uncountable</bracket><D>a university where you can study for a degree after you finish high school:</D> <X>a private/public college</X><dot><X>college students</X><dot><br><X>a college campus</X><dot><X>He first got interested in politics when he was in college.</X><NR>2.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>one of the main divisions of some large universities:</D> <X>The history department is part of the College of Arts and Sciences.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>colorful</H><audio>colorful.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>with bright colors; full of color:</D> <X>a colorful shirt</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>come</H><audio>come.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS>(<i>past </i><DR>came</DR><audio>came.mp3</audio>; <i>past participle </i><DR>come</DR><audio>come.mp3</audio>) <NR>1.</NR><D>to move to or toward the person who is speaking or the place that somebody is talking about:</D> <X>Come here!</X><dot><X>Come (and) look at this.</X><dot><X>I hope you can come to my party.</X><dot><X>They're coming to stay for a week.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to arrive or reach a place:</D> <X>What time are you coming home?</X><dot><X>Did the newspaper come yet? </X> <CF>how come ...?</CF> (<i>informal</i>) <D>why or how:</D> <X>How come you're back so early?</X><dot><X>How come I didn't get one too? </X> <CF>come back</CF> <D>to return:</D> <X>I don't know what time I'll be coming back. </X> <CF>come from ...</CF> <D>to live in or have been born in a place:</D> <X>Where do you come from originally?</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>comfortable</H><audio>comfortable.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>allowing you to feel relaxed and providing you with everything your body needs:</D> <X>Our hotel room was large and comfortable.</X><dot><X>a comfortable temperature</X> (= not too hot or too cold)<dot><X>Sit down and make yourselves comfortable.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>complete</H><su>1</su><audio>complete.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>to make something whole:</D> <X>We need two more players to complete the team.</X><dot><X>I finally managed to complete my collection.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to finish something; to bring something to an end:</D> <X>When the building has been completed, it will look impressive.</X><dot><X>He completed medical school in 2005.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>to fill out something (e.g. a form):</D> <X>Please complete the following questionnaire in capital letters.</X><dot><X>Completed application forms should be received by December 9.</X><H>complete</H><su>2</su><audio>complete.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>having or including all parts; with nothing missing:</D> <X>I gave a complete list of the stolen items to the police.</X><dot><X>The book explains the complete history of the place.</X><NR>2.</NR>(not before a noun) <D>finished or ended:</D> <X>The investigation should be complete by Friday.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>(only before a noun) as great as is possible; total; in every way:</D> <X>the complete reorganization of the department</X><dot><X>It was a complete waste of time.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>completely</H><audio>completely.mp3</audio><PS>adverb</PS><D>as much as is possible; totally; in every way:</D> <X>The building was completely destroyed by fire.</X><dot><X>We're trying a completely new method.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>concert</H><audio>concert.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a performance of music:</D> <X>a rock concert</X><dot><X>The concert was held in Central Park.</X><dot><X>The orchestra is giving concerts in Cleveland, Columbus, and Cincinnati.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>considerate</H><audio>considerate.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>careful not to upset people; thinking of others:</D> <X>It was very considerate of you to offer to drive me home.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>convenience store</H><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a store that sells food, magazines and other small items, and stays open longer than other stores</D> ]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>conversation</H><audio>conversation.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable, uncountable</bracket><D>informal talk:</D> <bracket>countable</bracket><X>I had a long conversation with her about her plans for the future.</X><dot><bracket>uncountable</bracket><X>His job is his only topic of conversation.</X><dot><X>She finds it difficult to make conversation.</X> (= to think of things to say)]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cook</H><audio>cook.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>to prepare food for eating by heating it:</D> <X>My mother taught me how to cook.</X><dot><X>He cooked us a meal.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>(used about food) to be prepared for eating by being heated:</D> <X>I could smell something cooking in the kitchen.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cool</H><audio>cool.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><NR>1.</NR>(<i>informal</i>) <D>very good; excellent:</D> <X>What a cool car!</X><dot><X>"There's a party at Dave's tonight." "Cool!"</X><NR>2.</NR>(<i>informal</i>) <D>fashionable; popular:</D> <X>A lot of kids think that smoking makes them look cool.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>calm; not excited or affected by strong emotions:</D> <X>She always manages to remain cool under pressure.</X><NR>4.</NR><D>fairly cold; not hot or warm:</D> <X>It was a cool evening, so I put on a sweater.</X><dot><X>This product should be stored in a cool place.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>corner</H><audio>corner.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a place where two lines, edges, surfaces, or roads meet:</D> <X>in a corner of the room</X><dot><X>Write your address in the upper right-hand corner.</X><dot><X>The office is on the corner of Fifth Avenue and 35th Street.</X><dot><X>There's a mailbox around the corner on Walnut Street.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>correct</H><su>1</su><audio>correct.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>with no mistakes; right or true:</D> <X>Good job! All your answers were correct.</X><dot><X>Be sure you put the correct address on the envelope.</X><H>correct</H><su>2</su><audio>correct.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><NR>1.</NR><D>to make a mistake, fault, etc. right or better:</D> <X>to correct a spelling mistake</X><dot><X>to correct a test</X> (= to mark the mistakes in it) <NR>2.</NR><D>to point out the mistakes or faults of somebody:</D> <X>He's always correcting me when I say something wrong.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>couch</H><audio>couch.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a comfortable seat with a back and arms. It is long enough for two or more people to sit on; sofa:</D> <X>Don't let the dog sit on the couch!</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>country</H><audio>country.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS>(<i>plural </i><DR>countries</DR>) <NR>1.</NR><bracket>countable</bracket><D>an area of land with its own people, government, etc.:</D> <X>Argentina, Brazil, and other South American countries</X><dot><X>There was snow over the northern part of the country last night.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>land which is away from towns and cities:</D> <X>Do you live in the city or the country?</X><dot><X>country life</X><NR>3.</NR><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>an area of land (especially considering its physical features):</D> <X>miles of open country</X><dot><X>hilly country</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>crowded</H><audio>crowded.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>full of people:</D> <X>The mall was crowded with holiday shoppers.</X><dot><X>a crowded bus</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>curl</H><audio>curl.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a piece of hair that curves around:</D> <X>Her hair fell in curls around her face.</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>curly</H><audio>curly.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS>(<DR>curlier</DR>; <DR>curliest</DR>) <D>full of curls; shaped like a curl:</D> <X>curly hair</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cute</H><audio>cute.mp3</audio><PS>adjective</PS><D>attractive; good-looking:</D> <X>Your little girl is so cute!</X><dot><X>Check out those cute guys over there!</X><dot><X>a cute dress</X>]]></ENTRY><ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>cycle</H><audio>cycle.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS><D>to ride a bicycle, especially as a sport</D> ]]></ENTRY></words>