<words>
<ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>karaoke</H><audio>karaoke.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>uncountable</bracket><D>a type of entertainment in which a machine plays only the music of popular songs so that people can sing the words themselves</D> ]]></ENTRY>  
<ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>keep</H><audio>keep.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS>(<i>past</i>, <i>past participle </i><DR>kept</DR><audio>kept.mp3</audio>) <NR>1.</NR><D>to continue to have something, permanently or for a period of time:</D> <X>You can keep that pen. I don't need it anymore.</X><dot><X>Can I keep the car until next week?</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to continue to be in a particular state or position:</D> <X>You need to keep warm.</X><dot><X>That boy can't keep still.</X><dot><X>Keep close to me and we won't get separated.</X>]]></ENTRY>
<ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>kind</H><audio>kind.mp3</audio><PS>noun</PS><bracket>countable</bracket><D>a group whose members all have the same qualities:</D> <X>The concert attracted people of all kinds.</X><dot><X>The concert attracted all kinds of people.</X><dot><X>Many kinds of plants and animals are being lost every year.</X><dot><X>I'm interested in all different kinds of music.</X>]]></ENTRY>
<ENTRY><![CDATA[<H>know</H><audio>know.mp3</audio><PS>verb</PS>(<i>past </i><DR>knew</DR><audio>knew.mp3</audio>; <i>past participle </i><DR>known</DR><audio>known.mp3</audio>) (not in the continuous tenses) <NR>1.</NR><D>to have knowledge or information in your mind:</D> <X>I don't know much about sports.</X><dot><X>Do you know their telephone number?</X><dot><X>Did you know that Jon enjoyed painting?</X><NR>2.</NR><D>to have met or seen somebody before:</D> <X>We've known each other for years.</X><NR>3.</NR><D>to be familiar with a place:</D> <X>I don't know this part of the city well.</X><NR>4.</NR><D>to speak or understand a language:</D> <X>I don't know much Spanish.</X><NR>5.</NR><D>to be able to do something:</D> <X>Do you know how to swim?</X><ID>you know</ID> (<i>informal</i>) <NR>1.</NR><D>(used when the speaker is thinking of what to say next):</D> <X>Well, you know, it's kind of hard to explain.</X><NR>2.</NR><D>(used when the speaker wants to check whether somebody understands what he/she is saying):</D> <X>It just makes me really mad, you know?</X><dot><br><X>I bought one of those new bread machines, you know, like the one Mike has.</X>]]></ENTRY>
</words>